okay so thank you for joining this
好的，谢谢您的加入
session so we like to do it at Eclipse
会议，所以我们喜欢在Eclipse上做
conference so we have this keynote
会议，所以我们有这个主题演讲
torque at the beginning of the afternoon
下午开始时的扭矩
and after we splitting incisions and we
在分割切口后，我们
join again before before going outside
在出门前再次加入
for for the reception we usually join
为了我们通常参加的招待会
again for ignite talks so what is an
再次引发对话，那么什么是
ignite talk the definition is 20 slides
点燃谈话，定义为20张幻灯片
15 seconds per slide and so it lasts for
每张幻灯片15秒，因此持续
five minutes and the strides run
五分钟，大步向前
automatically so we have six ignites
自动，所以我们有六个点火
plus a special today and so well the
再加上今天的特别优惠
Mikkel will be the first ones and we
Mikkel将是第一个，我们
have Clemmie
有克莱米
atif yen's Kevin emini and so that's
atif yen的Kevin emini，所以
that's an experience I think for as a
我认为这是一种经验
speaker actually I've never done that so
演讲者实际上我从未这样做过
I don't know but I appreciate the
我不知道，但我感谢
challenge of each each speaker except
每个演讲者的挑战，除了
every year to do it
每年要做
and so yeah just again we have the
所以是的，我们再次有了
reception tonight at La Tomatina the
今晚在La Tomatina举行的招待会
bogus which is a nice tapas bar so
假的，这是一个不错的西班牙小吃吧
that's a private party for those of you
那是你们的私人聚会
already went there so we have the
已经去了那里，所以我们有
weather looks good and we would have all
天气看起来不错，我们将拥有所有
the terrace and so not too bad it's not
露台，所以还不错，不是
raining so we can enjoy the terrace and
下着雨，所以我们可以享受露台和
and so thanks again to IBM for for
因此，再次感谢IBM的支持
sponsoring this reception you when you
当你赞助这个招待会
go out of the of the room you will have
走出你将要拥有的房间
this small postcard with the address and
这个小明信片，上面有地址和
everything you need to go there so I
你需要去那里的一切，所以我
think I'm done for the moment and the
认为我已经完成了，
first guy to try it is Mitchell era and
第一个尝试的人是米切尔时代，
so I give you the mic and I just press :
所以我给你麦克风，然后按：
whatever you want
无论你想要什么
and go okay hi everyone I'm in Carroll
好的，大家好，我在卡罗尔（Carroll）
and I'm here to tell you about ID as a
我在这里告诉您有关ID的信息
front-end and first time to Marquette on
前端和第一次去Marquette
West report in Eclipse IDE we use
我们使用的Eclipse IDE中的West报告
language Java protocol takes May and CLI
语言Java协议需要May和CLI
and that's already been already been 15
到那时已经15岁了
seconds I guess okay some reminders
秒，我想可以提醒一下
before we get started what is the
在我们开始之前，什么是
language of a protocol you probably
您可能使用的协议语言
already heard of it it's a protocol
已经听说过这是一个协议
between a client which would be the IDE
之间的客户端，这将是IDE
and a server containing the language
和包含该语言的服务器
logic the both communicate over messages
逻辑上两者都通过消息进行通信
which are standardized with request
根据要求标准化
response notification to get over N
响应通知以克服N
language value it turns the material n
语言的价值将物质变成n
times n integration into a star n plus M
倍n积分成星n加M
integration which given the amount of
给定的积分量
languages and tools supported devised by
支持的语言和工具
tender amount of integration to take
整合所需的投标量
care of this very interesting protocol
照顾这个非常有趣的协议
obviously became successful in Eclipse
显然在Eclipse中取得了成功
community so 11 eclipses the top
社区，所以11位居首位
projects are related to language of a
项目与语言有关
protocol providing either an SDK or an
提供SDK或
integration or a discovery or an ID but
集成或发现或ID，但
unfortunately along West Java protocol
不幸的是，沿西Java协议
is not enough because it doesn't cover
还不够，因为它没有涵盖
the syntax highlighting and you need
语法突出显示，您需要
extra stuff for that and that's what
多余的东西就是这样
textmate files are for text message are
textmate文件用于短信
Gramma's to configure syntax
语法配置语法
highlighting for a given file there are
突出显示给定文件
240 repository for text made files for
240个文本文件的存储库，用于
each each one containing one or more
每一个包含一个或多个
tech drama fault
科技剧错误
Eva's files and at least 4 IDs
Eva的文件和至少4个ID
supporting those textmate
支持那些同伴
files so it also became successful at
文件，因此它也成功在
eclipse with the Eclipse TM for a
用Eclipse TM蚀
project many which provide an
许多项目提供了
integration in the Eclipse IDE and also
集成在Eclipse IDE中
a plan Java integration if you want to
如果您想进行计划的Java集成
include this report for text made in
包含此报告中的文字
NetBeans or IntelliJ to name them
NetBeans或IntelliJ为其命名
another interesting vibe will be the
另一个有趣的氛围是
language configuration dot JSON which is
语言配置点JSON是
provided by vs code and they configure
由vs代码提供，它们进行配置
matching brackets commands and all other
括号匹配命令和所有其他
stuff you may like in your IDE and TM
您在IDE和TM中可能喜欢的东西
for e also add support for those files
对于e还要添加对这些文件的支持
in the Eclipse IDE finally we'll use the
最后，在Eclipse IDE中，我们将使用
generic editors that was introduced in
引入的通用编辑器
oxygen release which allows you to
氧气释放，使您能够
extend an Eclipse editor very easily
非常容易地扩展Eclipse编辑器
with plain gfs code and
用普通的gfs代码和
TM for e analyst before II do extend
II之前的e分析师TM
this editor those layers are all do has
这个编辑器的所有图层都是
allowed us to implement two new
允许我们实施两个新的
integrations for akley's photon with
akley的光子与
very low manpower which is about about
人力非常低，大约
two weeks from Lucas Glenn and I yeah
离卢卡斯·格伦（Lucas Glenn）和我两周
the first one will be the position in
第一个将是
Eclipse IDE with Eclipse acute acute
带有Eclipse的Eclipse IDE急性急性
embeds amnesia language server in
将失忆语言服务器嵌入
Eclipse IDE to provide the content
Eclipse IDE提供的内容
assist and so on and it also used the
协助等等，它也使用了
dotnet command line to integrate new
dotnet命令行以集成新的
without the bug new without export run
没有新的错误，没有导出运行
and so on for us it's the same
对我们来说都是一样的
architecture we used the rest language
我们使用其余语言的架构
server and text my gramma to get the
服务器并发短信给我的语法以获取
addition and cargo to provision and
补充和货物供应和
deploy projects and so on
部署项目等等
we also have support for debug we CDT
我们还支持CDT调试
integration because it relies on gdb and
集成，因为它依赖于gdb和
a dedicated package this is a very low
专用包装，这是一个非常低的
card architecture because everything is
卡架构，因为一切都是
done by DM 4e and the rest before you so
由DM 4e完成，其余则由您完成
you as a provider you would have to
您作为提供者，您将必须
compute only three files and this
仅计算三个文件，这
integration starts from 35 lines of God
整合从神的35行开始
this is the language of a protocol
这是协议的语言
integration you can start with five
整合可以从五个开始
lines of Java to start the server so you
Java行来启动服务器，因此您
just give the command to start the
只需给出命令即可启动
server and eleven lines of XML to define
服务器和11行XML来定义
the server and bind it to the file you
服务器并将其绑定到您的文件
need so here it would be binding to a
需要所以在这里它将绑定到
shop the textmate integration is about
商店的textmate集成是关于
declaring the text made file and binding
声明文本文件和绑定
it to the file you need 17 lines of XML
它到您需要17行XML的文件中
and the language configuration can be
语言配置可以是
born to a given file type with six lines
具有六行的给定文件类型
of each ma XML the LS the language
每个XML的LS语言
server can be provided in many way it
服务器可以通过多种方式提供
can be considered as a prerequisite
可以视为前提条件
under workstation or sheep with the
在工作站或羊与
plug-in or like a cute dog there is
插件或像可爱的狗一样
about a cool extra time it can be
大约很酷的额外时间
shipped as a plugin I can go slow it can
作为插件交付，我可以减慢它的速度
be shipped as a plug-in inside your
作为插件运送到您的内部
plug-in like a queue does or you can
插件就像队列一样，或者您可以
have inside your tool like corrosion
工具内部像腐蚀一样
dedicated without to provision your
专门不提供您的
language server and automatically
语言服务器并自动
install it on your workstation
将其安装在您的工作站上
you will you see this nice screenshot no
您会看到这个漂亮的屏幕截图吗？
no thanks
不用了，谢谢
so what does a benefit of this approach
那么这种方法的好处是什么
against the traditional rape layman
反对传统的强奸外行
language logic you get easier to
语言逻辑，使您更容易理解
implement feature a more consistent more
实现功能更加一致
reusability with better factorization
可重用性更好的分解
and a faster time to market for same
并加快上市时间
feature richness so what now for you you
功能丰富，现在为您服务
have to adopt this it applies to so many
必须采用它适用于很多
languages in it applies to so many tools
语言适用于许多工具
that this is a technology you need to
这是您需要的技术
rely on because it is extremely
依靠，因为它非常
successful and reduce the cost of doing
成功并降低成本
an integration what's next
整合下一步是什么
editing code is just one activity of or
编辑代码只是或的一项活动
job as developers there is also don't
作为开发人员的工作也没有
need to test to debug to provision new
需要测试以调试以提供新的
project to build and we are working we
项目建设，我们正在努力
touch the dev tools community is working
触摸开发工具社区正在工作
on new protocols for that so what to
为此的新协议上
remember if you fund that too long adopt
记住，如果您资助的时间太长，
existing technologies like language of a
现有技术，例如
protocol and textmate create standard
协议和文本伙伴创建标准
artifact like on West Java and text my
像在West Java上的工件和文本my
grandma's create clients for those
奶奶为那些人创造客户
technologies and integrate them together
技术并将它们集成在一起
and your favorite ideas with very few
和你最喜欢的想法很少
lines of code Thanks
代码行谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
so I guess that I have to do something
所以我想我必须做点什么
okay
好的
[Music]
[音乐]
okay should be good sequel vision
好的应该是续集的远见
reactive landscape that's it
就是反应式景观
okay so the next picture is Cremo
好吧，下一张照片是Cremo
Escoffier and we're at hello my name is
埃斯科菲耶，我们打招呼，我叫
Clemens Kofi fasten your seat belt
Clemens Kofi系好安全带
because in five minutes I will tell you
因为五分钟后我会告诉你
what being reactive means because in the
反应是什么意思，因为在
last few years almost everything and his
最近几年几乎所有的东西和他的
dog became suddenly reactive it started
狗突然反应了，它开始了
with reactive manifestos that has
反应性宣言
defined active systems then we are
定义活动系统，那么我们就是
reactive spring reactive programming or
反应性弹簧反应性编程或
active extension or active streams and
活动扩展或活动流，以及
all those reactive has been associated
所有那些反应性的都与之相关
with different concepts a touch miss
不同的概念碰触小姐
edge resilient scalability data flows
边缘弹性可伸缩性数据流
spreadsheets events actors and so on so
电子表格事件参与者等
such a lot of practice but if you look
这么多的练习，但是如果你看
at the oxford dictionary to know what
在牛津字典里知道什么
reactive means rectory is defined as
反应式直肠定义为
showing a response to schemas so if we
显示对模式的响应
apply this definition to software we can
将此定义应用于我们可以
simply say that directive software is a
简单地说，指令软件是
software showing responses to stimuli
显示对刺激有反应的软件
such as user inputs advanced users and
例如用户输入高级用户和
so on and you can say well since the
等等，自从
early edge of software we are building
我们正在构建的软件的早期优势
reactive system as it's a girl of
反应系统，因为它是一个女孩
software to obey to the user and to
服从用户并遵守的软件
operating system and you write waiver in
操作系统，您在其中写弃权
the last few years we are three main
最近几年我们是三个主要
clusters that are emails around this
围绕电子邮件的集群
reactive birth world first were active
反应性出生世界首先活跃
systems which is an accurate
准确的系统
architectural style to build distributed
建筑风格打造分布式
system right then we add corrective
系统，然后我们添加纠正措施
programming which is an API for a
编程，这是用于
synchronous development and then we have
同步发展，然后我们有
reactive streams which help you making
反应性流可以帮助您
your system works because when you are
您的系统正常工作是因为
using relative programming back pressure
使用相对编程背压
is has to be managed we are going to see
必须进行管理，我们将要看到
that but let's start with reactive
那，让我们从反应开始
system reactive system infuse a
系统无功系统注入
synchrony at the core of your system by
通过您的系统核心实现同步
using a synchronous message spacing
使用同步消息间隔
between all your components because you
在所有组件之间，因为您
have this you can be elastic and you can
有了这个，你可以变得有弹性，你可以
be resilient and this give you
有弹性，这给你
responsiveness so basically with this
基本上就是这样
you are building a systems that will
您正在建立一个可以
stay responsive in phase of failures and
在故障阶段保持响应，
under free training loads so basically
在基本上免费的训练负荷下
this is what you want to be
这就是你想要的
whoever to do that direct user failures
这样做的直接用户失败者
load and so on you need to react and you
负载等等，您需要做出反应，您
need to react as synchronously and one
需要像一个人一样同步反应
thing you need to understand is that as
您需要了解的是
synchronous doesn't mean a floating walk
同步并不意味着步行
to unthread pool this is what we are
释放池这就是我们
doing for yes as it doesn't work it's
做是的，因为它不起作用是
limit your scalability as synchronous
将您的可扩展性限制为同步
means never black because if you use
表示永远不会变黑，因为如果您使用
threads then you are going to spend lots
线程，那么你将花费很多
of time waiting and waiting and waiting
时间的等待和等待的等待
and 200 concurrent concurrent requests
和200个并发并发请求
you need to have many many threads this
你需要有很多很多线程
is going to consume memory CPU cycles
将消耗内存CPU周期
because of the contact switch it's not
因为有接触开关
going to work the execution a
去执行执行
synchronous execution model is going to
同步执行模型将
divide use your tasks into chunks and
将您的任务分成多个部分，
always make progress because it's rely
总是取得进展，因为这取决于
on non-blocking i/o whoever physician in
在无阻塞的I / O医师中
task based concurrency and then a
基于任务的并发，然后
synchronous programming model this is
这是同步编程模型
what its vertex is about let's focus a
它的顶点是关于什么
little bit of what a synchronous
一点点的同步
programming models it all start with
编程模型都始于
scarbacks don't use callbacks then we
Scarback不使用回调，那么我们
have futures and promises we are
有未来和承诺，我们是
reactive programming and we have more
反应式编程，我们还有更多
advanced techniques such as co-routine
协同例程等高级技术
and fibers we are going to focus on
和纤维，我们将专注于
reactive programming because if so talk
反应式编程，因为如果这么说
about reactive reactive programming use
关于反应式反应式编程的使用
the concept of data streams to
数据流的概念
orchestrate all your logic so you are
协调您的所有逻辑，以便您
going to create new data streams you are
将要创建新的数据流
going to combine and transform data
将要合并和转换数据
streams and then you're going to observe
流，然后您将观察
them so during this observation you can
他们，所以在这次观察中，您可以
have three things it can you can have
有三件事你可以拥有
data you can have failures and you can
数据可能会导致失败，并且您可以
have completion for bonded streams so
绑定流已经完成，所以
this is a very low api and you don't
这是一个非常低的api，您不会
really want to develop all your software
真的想开发您所有的软件
which can using such kind of API
可以使用这种API
fortunately there is many libraries
幸运的是有很多图书馆
providing lots of operators such as
提供许多运营商，例如
extremes eric java 2 and pivotal reactor
极端eric Java 2和枢轴反应堆
what that combines the best ideas from
什么结合了来自最好的想法
the observer pattern iterator pattern
观察者模式迭代器模式
and functional programming don't be
和函数式编程不一样
afraid bad functional but that gave you
害怕功能不好，但这给了你
a lot of return and you can be really
很多回报，您可以真正
really efficient with that small issue
那个小问题真的很有效
is data data streams if you have a slow
是数据数据流，如果速度较慢
consumer and a fast producer what would
消费者和快速生产者
happen it will die because it's going to
发生它会死，因为它将
prefer all the events that you cannot
喜欢所有你不能做的事情
keep up and then you have no memory
跟上，然后你就没有记忆
anymore
不再
fortunately we have raki streams that
幸运的是，我们有raki流
define a non-breaking and a synchronous
定义不间断和同步
pressure protocols that led to slow
导致缓慢的压力协议
consumer hotel - the first producer when
消费型酒店-第一家生产商
it is ready to under load so this way
准备好承受负载，这样
you are going to auto pace your system
您将自动调整系统速度
very very nicely so let's summarize
非常非常好，让我们总结一下
being reactive means being a synchronous
反应性意味着同步
what you want to build is our active
您想要建立的是我们的主动
system systems that stay responsive in
保持响应的系统系统
front of filtering load and failures for
过滤负载和故障的前端
this you can use right extremes for back
这个你可以用正确的极限
pressure no active programming as a way
没有主动编程的压力
to develop such kind of a synchronous
发展这种同步
system whoever superpowers does not come
谁没有超级大国
from free it's completely shifting how
从免费到完全改变了
you develop software from H and B to be
您从H和B开发软件
exchanged by B by a it's very hard at
由B交换，很难
the banging but as soon as you reach the
砰的一声，但一旦你到达
first level you become a superior that's
第一阶段，你成为上级
what I have if you're interested to go a
如果您有兴趣去的话，我有什么
little bit deeper on this topic I have
我对这个话题有更深入的了解
two tours tomorrow one about building or
明天有两次旅行，一个是关于建筑的
active system on top of kubernetes and
在kubernetes之上的活动系统和
the other one about event reactive event
另一个关于事件反应性事件
sourcing and security
采购与安全
thank you
谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
so thanks cream all
所以谢谢所有
okay so the next talk is by Mahmoud
好吧，下一个话题是马哈茂德
ative Javed and yeah let's let's go
贾维德（Javed）亲爱的，让我们走吧
good afternoon okay
下午好
my name is Artie and I am opposed to
我叫Artie，我反对
crow researcher at melatonin university
褪黑素大学的乌鸦研究员
Sweden and I'm going to talk about
瑞典，我要谈一谈
migration or Eclipse process framework
迁移或Eclipse流程框架
composer so what is e PF composer for
作曲家，什么是e PF作曲家？
those who are not aware it is
那些不知道的是
specifically dwelt for process engineers
专为工艺工程师而设
and project managers to provide support
和项目经理提供支持
for authoring carrying and deploying
用于创作携带和部署
software system development processes in
软件系统开发流程
the compose approach we have the method
组合方法，我们有方法
contents like tasks roles work products
诸如任务，角色，工作产品之类的内容
based on which the processes are
基于哪个过程
assembled and then they are configured
组装，然后进行配置
the method library contains and the
方法库包含和
process seasonal processes based for the
处理基于
specific project needs and then
具体项目需求，然后
published for the enactment as process
为制定过程而出版
planner project documentation so EPF
规划师项目文档，因此EPF
composer is based on the unified method
作曲者基于统一方法
architecture metamodel which supports
支持的架构元模型
major parts of the OMG spam 2.0 APF
OMG垃圾邮件2.0 APF的主要部分
composer actually is not evolved from
作曲家实际上不是从
log time 11 years and also it has
记录时间11年，也有
attracted considerable attention from
引起了来自
from I mean industries and Adam is from
我的意思是工业，而亚当来自
the people worldwide it is it is I mean
我是说全世界的人
still based on the older versions of
仍基于旧版本
technologies and it was reducing the
技术，它正在减少
interests in the community so in the
在社区的利益，所以在
context of the mass project the
大规模项目的背景
migration of EPF composer is required to
需要迁移EPF作曲家才能
build an ecosystem and very integrating
建立一个生态系统并且高度整合
besides the others in in the mass
除了群众中的其他人
platform for example in the context of
平台，例如
the mask platform we are we need the EPF
面具平台，我们需要EPF
composer to support the tasks like
作曲家支持诸如
management of Emmys or lines reuse
艾美奖或线路重用的管理
assistant and discovery and compliance
助理，发现与合规
management in order to perform the
管理以执行
migration the decision is taken in the
迁移决定是在
context of the mass project and we have
大规模项目的背景，我们有
established a collaborative relationship
建立合作关系
with the IBM team
与IBM团队一起
yes and the migration is planned in four
是的，计划在四个月内完成迁移
phases at the first payers we decided to
我们决定在第一个付款方分阶段进行
resolve the source code problems then at
解决源代码问题，然后在
the next phase we decided to resolve the
下一阶段，我们决定解决
problems with the content storage then
然后内容存储出现问题
the configuration combo box problems
配置组合框问题
rich text editor problems and finally to
富文本编辑器的问题，最后到
export the standalone application at the
在以下位置导出独立应用程序
very first step the required software's
第一步，所需的软件
needed to be installed for the release
需要安装该版本
for which we have used the software site
我们已经为此软件站点使用过
repository and then the problems for the
存储库，然后针对
source code have been resolved for the
源代码已被解析为
complete list of changes and
完整的更改列表和
applications which we have resolved
我们已经解决的申请
there is an Bugzilla post at the next
下一个有一个Bugzilla帖子
light yes to be visited
可以参观
if you've composers towards the method
如果您是作曲家
library contains in their own folders
库包含在自己的文件夹中
and files so for the new Eclipse
和文件，因此对于新的Eclipse
released we are also getting the
发布我们也得到了
problems for storage of method library
方法库的存储问题
contains due to the I mean due to the
包含由于我的意思是由于
conflicting scheduling rules which we
我们有冲突的调度规则
have resolved and the problems were also
已经解决，问题也
resolved for the combo box of Eclipse
解决了Eclipse的组合框
process prima composer which sports
原始运动的作曲家
users in selecting the specific subset
用户选择特定子集
of the method library and the problems
方法库的介绍和存在的问题
are also resolved for the rich text
也针对富文本格式进行了解析
editor of EPF composer and in the next
EPF作曲家的编辑，下一篇
step the last step the incompatible
最后一步，不兼容
bundles are removed replacing bundles
删除捆绑包，替换捆绑包
already under the applications I resolve
已经在我解决的应用程序下
to export the standalone application yes
导出独立应用程序是
this contribution is acknowledged by the
该贡献得到了
IBM but ok UPF composer is launched as a
IBM，但好的UPF作曲者是作为
standalone application but also in the
独立应用程序，也可以在
Eclipse IDE we would like to mention
我们要提到的Eclipse IDE
that the UPF composer has been
UPF作曲家
integrated in the amaz open to platform
集成在Amazon开放平台中
the acknowledgement is given at the EPF
在EPF上给出确认
website also the committed status is
网站的承诺状态为
assigned for the project
分配给项目
APF composer is evolved to the new
APF作曲家发展到新的
technology versions the further
技术进一步发展
enhancements can be done based on the
增强可以基于
user and technology needs for example
用户和技术需求
the complete sport first BAM 2.0 and the
完整的运动优先BAM 2.0和
integration for studio model episode 3
工作室模型第3集的集成
can be considered thank you very much
可以说非常感谢你
for your attention
为了您的关注
[Applause]
[掌声]
Thank You ativ maybe just one comment
谢谢ativ也许只有一条评论
because what I like in this in this
因为我喜欢这个
project is that that's that's a research
项目就是那是一项研究
project we the Eclipse Foundation is
Eclipse Foundation是我们的项目
also a partner of the research project
也是该研究项目的合作伙伴
so you can meet them at the Eclipse
所以你可以在Eclipse遇到他们
research corner but also that's a good
研究角，但这也很好
example of one of the great advantages
优势之一的例子
of Eclipse as a foundation that EPF was
Eclipse作为EPF的基础
not very active for a long time and then
长时间不活跃，然后
new people come and we managed to
新来的人，我们设法
establish this relationship on three
在三个方面建立这种关系
continents and that's and that works and
大洲，那是那行得通，
we have we are one Bondy of new nuco
我们拥有我们是新努科的邦迪
meters so that's that's pretty cool so
米，那很酷，所以
yes it's your turn thank you very much
是的，轮到你了，非常感谢
yeah go ahead so I will be talking about
是的，所以我会在谈论
the SN io team so we're talking about
SN io团队，所以我们正在谈论
security for Eclipse project so when it
Eclipse项目的安全性
comes to eclipse projects it may be at
来蚀它可能在
some time that people come along and
有人来了一段时间
they report a security issue with your
他们报告您的安全问题
project or a vulnerable voltner ability
项目或脆弱的伏特纳人能力
that takes one to two plant so someone
需要一到两棵植物，所以有人
reports something which is oh my god
报告某事是我的上帝
this is like completely insane it's
就像完全疯了一样
completely broken so what do you do so
完全坏了，你怎么办
you put something in a change lock more
你把一些东西放在变更锁里
qualified which says okay this there's
合格的，说好的，这是
something wrong yeah we open it that and
是的，是的，我们打开它，然后
then it takes a while and then you
然后需要一段时间，然后你
actually release at some point later on
实际上稍后发布
so there is a time delay between the
因此，
report the actual fixing or the
报告实际修复或
qualifier done and so it will take a
预选赛完成，因此需要一个
while and there's a day so one way to
有一天，所以有一种方法
handle this is pretty simple you just
处理这很简单
write in packages and performance
写包装和性能
improvements we wake no worries no one
改进，我们唤醒，无后顾之忧
will notice so we really you have a look
会注意到的，所以我们真的您可以看看
at the change lock and you don't have
在变更锁处，而您没有
any specific information in there I
那里的任何具体信息
don't think that's the right way to do
认为这不是正确的方法
because there are a few answers well
因为有一些答案
there aren't as missing to to those
那些人并不缺少
questions like which components are
诸如哪些组件是问题
affected does it affect me so what
会影响我吗
actually was wrong if you just put in
如果你只是放进去实际上是错的
something awake you have no idea how
醒着的你不知道如何
serious that is so the idea is to have a
认真的，所以想法是要有一个
CVE and a CV ID which exactly identifies
CVE和可准确识别的CV ID
that problem so you have a CV ID and
这个问题，所以您有简历ID，
here's an example of a CV ID for example
这是一个CV ID的示例
for Eclipse mosquito so it keeps
Eclipse蚊子，让它保持
mosquito handsome issue there was some
蚊子英俊的问题有一些
report coming in like oh this is like
报告进来像哦，这就像
completely insecure and there's a CV ID
完全不安全，有简历ID
assigned and you can write it'll change
分配，你可以写它会改变
lock simply like we have a fix for CPU
就像我们已经修复了CPU一样锁定
number this and that and later on you
编号这个和那个，然后在你身上
can also qualify like okay this evey
也可以像这样确定资格
year has been fixed in those and these
这些年已经确定
mosquito versions were affected so this
蚊子的版本受到影响，所以这
is how soft still no one at that point
那时还没有人有多软
knows what actually was wrong later on
知道以后到底出了什么问题
you do a disclosure what
你披露什么
this actually was and different
这实际上是不同的
different other groups will pick that up
其他不同的团体会接手
so for example you have um if you google
例如，如果您有Google，
for that CV ID you will get for example
对于该简历ID，您将获得例如
Debian security tracker which refers to
Debian安全追踪器，指的是
that CV ID so you do know that okay this
该简历ID，所以您确实知道
is in Debian this is fixed in Debian
在Debian中已修复
shipped
已运送
also we have the different other the the
我们也有不同的其他
NV D which is the database tracking
NV D是数据库跟踪
those CV IDs from a different
那些来自其他网站的简历ID
perspective so the Eclipse Foundation
视角，因此Eclipse Foundation
has become a CNA and a CNA is a CV
已经成为CNA，而CNA是CV
numbering authority that is what already
已经是编号机构
happened
发生了
so the Eclipse Foundation can assign
因此Eclipse Foundation可以分配
those CV idea IDs to projects now what
那些用于项目的简历创意ID现在
you need for that is like like a small
你需要的就像一个小
description about what was wrong and you
有关您和您出了什么问题的描述
need to score and the score is the CB SS
需要得分，得分是CB SS
which like there's a few factors which
就像有几个因素
you can type into some webui and it
您可以输入一些webui，
spits out the severity of that issue so
吐出该问题的严重性，因此
everyone knows okay how serious is that
大家都知道，那有多严重
so even without disclosing anything
所以即使不公开任何东西
about the actual problem but you do know
关于实际问题，但您确实知道
okay if it's a CB SS of nine point
好吧，如果它是九点的CB SS
whatever you should take it seriously
不管你应该认真对待
so there's security at eclipse this has
所以在eclipse上有安全性
always been there so there were also a
一直在那里，所以也有一个
way how to report that there's a webpage
如何报告有一个网页
which you should probably have a look at
您可能应该看看
which explains what you do and you
解释了你的工作和你
should link to that from a project
应该链接到项目中的链接
perspective to point people towards okay
使人们指向好的观点
you have an issue please report it in
您有问题请在
that way so actually for for the IOT
这样，对于物联网来说
projects we do make that mandatory
我们确实将其强制性的项目
because we think that there should be in
因为我们认为应该在
SN IOT so CVS at eclipse how do we
SN IOT，所以eclipse的CVS我们如何
progress how would they process that you
进步他们将如何处理您
have to send an email to security at
必须向安全部门发送电子邮件
eclipse.org mention that you would like
eclipse.org提到您想要
to have that assigned we can assign that
要分配那个，我们可以分配那个
using Bugzilla so we need a process to
使用Bugzilla，因此我们需要一个流程来
ensure that CV ID is not assigned in
确保未分配CV ID
duplicate way so we use bugzilla the
复制方式，所以我们使用bugzilla
alias of that and a few years in get up
别名和几年起床
issues you still have to create an issue
问题，您仍然必须创建一个问题
in Bugzilla so we can do that for you
在Bugzilla中，我们可以为您做到这一点
but you can do it yourself and we have
但是你可以自己做，我们有
the product community
产品社区
and the component vulnerability reports
和组件漏洞报告
so what you can do later on is the to
所以您以后可以做的是
have the the I think that some some
有我认为一些
flack in Bugzilla which makes it not
Bugzilla中出现故障，这使其无法
accessible to the outside world but
对外开放，但
later on it will be disclosed and and
稍后将予以披露，并且
available to the public so beyond that
可供公众使用
there's right now no form a process
现在没有任何流程
about how to do that so this is just
关于如何做到这一点，这仅仅是
explained it how we do it up until now
解释了它到目前为止我们是如何做的
if you have any ideas come along and
如果您有任何想法，
talk to us and there's also a back which
与我们交谈，还有一个背后
you can track which is like Wayne Beaton
你可以追踪像韦恩·比顿
doing some some improvement on the
做一些改进
documentation around that so that we can
有关的文档，以便我们可以
point people towards that how that could
向人们指出那怎么可能
work and and how you can implement that
工作，以及如何实现
for your eclipse project and I have some
为你的日食项目，我有一些
time left awesome thank you so
时间太棒了，谢谢你
so next one is giving okay ready okay so
所以下一个给的准备好了吧
if any of you know what speed dating is
如果你们知道速配是什么
I need audience participation you guys
我需要观众参与
are going to be interviewing me for a
将要采访我
speed date okay
速度日期还可以
so when this comes up there's going to
因此，当出现这种情况时，
be a statement at the top and face says
在顶部发表声明，面对说
audience and bright-red
观众和鲜红色
like this then you would respond or you
这样，你会回应还是你
would yell out okay
会大声喊出来
so that's going to help me keep on track
这样可以帮助我保持正轨
as well so I need the audience
我也需要听众
participation to do this so hopefully by
希望如此参与
the end of this little speed-dating
这个小小的约会约会的结束
then come on guys okay thank you so my
那来吧，伙计们，好的，谢谢，所以我的
name is Jakarta ee and I am the new
我叫雅加达ee，我是新来的
future location of cloud native Java we
云原生Java的未来位置
will be developing micro services in the
将在开发微服务
cloud for the cloud promote innovation
云为云促创新
have releases much more common and often
有更常见的版本
than Java EE and we want to get the
而不是Java EE，我们希望获得
community involved
社区参与
okay okay best attributes okay so
好的，好的属性，好的，所以
definitely want to be innovative we want
绝对想要创新，我们想要
to have releases come out more often we
发行更多的东西，我们
want to get ideas from the community we
希望从社区中获得想法
want to participate with you we want to
想和你一起参加我们想
be more agile and flexible okay so we
变得更加敏捷和灵活，所以我们
want to be able to interact more with
希望能够与更多人互动
the community and make sure that you
社区并确保您
guys are that we're doing what you want
伙计们，我们正在做你想要的
to but we still need to be compatible
到，但我们仍然需要兼容
with previous versions thank you okay
与以前的版本谢谢你好
previous relationships yes I been
以前的关系是的
involved with them with one for a long
与他们长期牵扯在一起
time about about 20 years but we've
时间大约20年，但我们
decided to move on and now I'm kind of
决定继续前进，现在我有点
I'm hooked up with the Eclipse
我迷上了Eclipse
Foundation but I still like to keep
基金会，但我仍然喜欢保留
friends with old relationships so you
与旧有关系的朋友，所以你
can see that Oracle is still up there
可以看到甲骨文还在
okay so there's there's still a friend
好吧，那里还有一个朋友
okay so this is I have 39 kids okay and
好的，这是我有39个孩子，好的，
and we just found out last week that
我们上周才发现
we're gonna have another one so so so
我们会再有一个这样的
there's a fortieth one coming if you
如果你有四十个
want to see how all my kids are doing
想看看我所有的孩子都好吗
we've got a URL and you can keep tabs on
我们有一个URL，您可以保持打开标签
all of the different projects that are
所有不同的项目
being developed under Eclipse for for
在Eclipse下为
Jakarta ee and for EE for J they're all
雅加达EE和J的EE都是
at different stages okay so yes we do
在不同的阶段好吧，是的，我们这样做
you might have heard of them I've talked
您可能听说过我所说的
about them a few times like a profile we
关于他们几次像个人资料，我们
consider a sibling but right now he's
考虑一个兄弟姐妹，但现在他是
kind of like outside of the family and
有点像在家庭之外
so little you know a little bit of a
很少你知道一点
trailblazer little rogue type project
开拓者小流氓类型项目
but we expect him to come in to the
但我们希望他能参加
jacquard EEE fold once we settle down a
我们安顿下来后，提花EEE折叠
little bit more okay so I've got a few
好一点，所以我有一些
of them
他们之中
the main one if you just want to get
主要的，如果你只是想得到
started with Jakarta go to Jakarta EEE
从雅加达开始去雅加达EEE
okay very simple to remember you go out
好，很简单，记得你出去
there that's a good starting point from
那里是一个很好的起点
there you can get to our working group
在那里您可以进入我们的工作组
definition so you can learn more about
定义，以便您可以了解更多有关
Jakarta ee but the other one that you
雅加达ee但另一个是你
might be most interested in is the top
可能最感兴趣的是顶部
level project and that's called EE for J
级项目，即所谓的EE for J
and if you go up to that website key for
如果您转到该网站的密钥
J then you'll get a full list okay so of
J，那么您将获得完整列表，这样
course we're happy with Java okay we're
当然，我们对Java感到满意，好吧，
going to stick with Java but we also
会坚持使用Java，但我们也
know that there are some other languages
知道还有其他一些语言
that are getting popular
越来越受欢迎
I'm Kotlin as you know if you want to
我叫科特林，你想知道吗
call the JVM derivative that's one that
将JVM派生称为
we're keeping tabs on um possibly from
我们一直在关注um可能来自
my could profile possibly for Jakarta
我可以为雅加达配置文件
and then we want to keep tabs with the
然后我们要保持与
cloud with kubernetes dr and st oh yeah
云与kubernetes dr和st哦，是的
so since this is speed dating you know
所以因为这是快速约会
there's a few other things that I'll
我还有其他一些事情
share with you one of them is you know
与你分享其中之一是你知道
where do I like to vacation
我想在哪里度假
of course Jakarta right favorite colors
当然，雅加达是最喜欢的颜色
blue and shades of orange are nice
蓝色和橙色阴影很好
favorite drink yeah I used to like
是我最喜欢的最喜欢的饮料
coffee a lot and you know it's still
很多咖啡，你知道它仍然
okay and if I ever win the lottery of
好吧，如果我中了彩票
course I'm going to donate it all to the
当然，我将全部捐献给
Eclipse Foundation okay so I think we're
Eclipse Foundation好吧，我想我们是
still not quite there for sharing phone
还不可以共享电话
numbers but but what I would like to do
数字，但我想做什么
is point you at our various mailing
是指您在我们的各种邮件中
lists in forums we've got one the the
在论坛列表中，我们有一个
most active one is Jakarta ee community
最活跃的一个是雅加达EE社区
we've got thousands of responses out
我们有成千上万的回应
there already so that's the main one to
已经在那里，所以这是主要的
go to you could hit the work group the
去你可以打到工作组
pmc has a mailing list and then all of
pmc有一个邮件列表，然后所有
the individual projects under e4j has a
e4j下的各个项目都有一个
mailing list to keep tabs with all of
邮件列表，以保持与所有标签
the projects thank you Kevin
项目谢谢凯文
it's 12 2 upon root homie who is Phyllis
这是12 2根亲戚菲利斯
Yvonne
伊冯娜
shorter equal wait a second
短等一秒钟
we may have a battery issue so okay okay
我们可能有电池问题，好吧好吧
ready okay okay I'm Emily ji working for
准备好了，好的，我是艾米莉·吉（Emily ji）
IBM based her screen they okay oh okay
IBM根据她的屏幕，他们好吧，好吧
Emma Emily Gia I welcome for IBM and
Emma Emily Gia欢迎来到IBM和
today I'm going to talk about micro
今天我要谈微
profile means to used to
配置文件意味着习惯
so micro profile is programming model
所以微轮廓是编程模型
for applications you still is an
对于应用程序，您仍然是
infrastructure and today I'm going to
基础设施，今天我要去
talk about the micro profile first so
先说说微轮廓
micro profile has this specifications
微型轮廓具有此规格
config for tolerance Health metrics the
配置公差健康指标
security or open trees you know pay Pia
安全性或开阔的树木，您知道要付Pia
and a rest client so in the next few
还有一个休息的顾客，所以在接下来的几个
slides that goes through and look at how
幻灯片，看看如何
it works so what is a service a mesh
它起作用了，所以什么是网格服务
history the kind of service smash is
历史上的服务粉碎是
kind of look at as a server to server
看起来像服务器到服务器
communications make sure the
通讯确保
communication the faster and safer and
沟通更快，更安全，
reliable and what does the service a
可靠，服务是什么
match do actually is a candle provide a
匹配做实际上是一支蜡烛提供
quality service like a make sure that
优质服务，例如确保
the service communication resilience and
服务通信弹性和
a secure and also easily as a kind of
一种安全，也很容易
policy enforcement history is the good
政策执行历史是好的
example the Slava smash it was designed
例如Slava粉碎的设计
to connect a manager and secure your
连接经理并保护您的安全
macro services and this year there will
宏观服务，今年将
be a yeasty window already's this is a
已经是一个发霉的窗户了，这是一个
big busy picture about the yeast your
关于酵母的忙碌图片
architecture basically in your macro
架构基本上在您的宏中
service you have a port and also use do
服务你有一个端口，也使用做
we inject a proxy and a hijacker the
我们注入一个代理和一个劫机者
traffic to ensure the quality service so
交通以确保优质的服务
macro profile provided is following
提供的宏配置文件如下
eight inspects and is a Israel provider
八人检查，是以色列的提供者
some these four steps like for tolerance
这四个步骤中的一些步骤，例如容忍度
matrix are open tracing and for
矩阵是开放式跟踪，用于
injection there's some overlap so we
注射有一些重叠，所以我们
said have a workgroup in macro profile
说在宏配置文件中有一个工作组
so we look at how to best engage these
所以我们看如何最有效地吸引这些人
two things and make sure they work
两件事，并确保它们起作用
together if you are interested in
如果你有兴趣的话
joining in this
参加这个
slavi smash workgroup this is like
斯拉夫粉碎工作组，这就像
mystical and micro profile you can see
您可以看到的神秘和微观轮廓
macro profile in the application you
您在应用程序中的宏配置文件
still is like a spiderweb so we need to
仍然像蜘蛛网，所以我们需要
make sure you still understand a micro
确保您仍然了解微型
micro pav work for you still so in the
微密镶为您服务，因此在
micro profile comfy you can see this a
微型个人资料很舒适，您可以看到一个
macro profile comfy you can inject the
宏配置文件舒适，您可以注入
configuration the configuration directly
直接配置
can be injected from kubernetes coming
可以从kubernetes注入
back so that's the gist you will use so
返回，这就是您要使用的要点
this is a house check you still also
这是房子检查你还是
really understand health and point truth
真正了解健康并指出真理
determine where that poor data healthy
确定不良数据在哪里健康
or not so this macro profile health
是否如此宏配置文件运行状况
checker will identify whether these the
检查器将确定这些
health or not healthy or not this is a
健康或不健康，这是一个
matrix so macro profile can provide
矩阵，以便宏配置文件可以提供
additional application related the
与之相关的其他应用
matrix so East you can display you can
矩阵，以便您可以显示东
use the permission to view it this is a
使用权限查看它这是一个
macro prefer open API
宏更喜欢开放式API
so basically application need to
所以基本上应用程序需要
advertise itself what do I do what kind
自我宣传我该做什么
of under point I am providing and
我要提供的
there's no conflict between macro
宏之间没有冲突
profile I used to and the next one is
我以前的个人资料，下一个是
the macro profit IWT this is a very nice
宏观利润内河这是一个非常好的
bag so macro profile makes sure the twg
袋，所以宏配置文件可以确保twg
will propagate the tokens and make sure
将传播令牌并确保
the down where the transport is secure
运输安全的地方
and this of Vanowen the open creasing
而Vanowen的这种开放式压痕
you still can make sure can see the
您仍然可以确保可以看到
trees suspense whoever in either
树木悬念中的任何一个
application to a disseminators micro
应用于微传播器
profile automatic out of the for you so
配置文件自动为您
the next why the for tolerance so you
接下来为什么要宽容所以你
still can do the three macro propagande
还是可以做到三宏宣传
with his fly by he still we all needed
带着他的苍蝇，我们仍然需要
to rely on the his macro profile for
依靠他的宏观资料
back to do the for back because he still
回到做背，因为他仍然
cannot do the other bigger difference is
不能做的另一个更大的不同是
the macro prefer handle also so for
宏也喜欢处理
tolerance and you still can only handle
宽容，你仍然只能应付
HTTP requests wrongly and also it
HTTP错误地请求
County to reach where timon and Sookie
到达蒂蒙和苏奇的县
the breaker so we look at the conflict
断路器，所以我们看一下冲突
and scenario which is just HTTP related
和与HTTP相关的场景
hero requests among the multiple accrue
英雄请求中的多个累积
service is so easy we see how can we
服务是如此简单，我们知道如何
cope with the conflict so the current
应付冲突，所以目前
estate is we can disable micro profile
房地产是我们可以禁用微配置文件
for horns just leave the full path so he
牛角就走了，所以他
still can like using steel for horns
仍然可以喜欢用钢做喇叭
however can rely on the foot back from
但是可以依靠脚从
macro profile this is the future this is
宏观概况，这是未来，这是
a current future we need your help
当前的未来，我们需要您的帮助
during the community so basically we
在社区中，所以基本上
want to go through mega profile for
想通过大型个人资料
tolerance as in can automatically
公差可以自动
generate Estill County rules and
生成Estill County规则并
automatically with this honor DevOps can
凭此荣誉自动运行DevOps可以
automatically change the parameters and
自动更改参数并
if he still can not handle the four
如果他仍然不能处理这四个
horns automatically dear applicants to
牛角自动亲爱的申请人
handle like HTTP for example I think
我认为像HTTP这样的处理
[Applause]
[掌声]
thanks Emily
谢谢艾米丽
so and thank you to our six super hero
所以，谢谢你给我们的六个超级英雄
of the of this afternoon and now we are
今天下午的时间，现在我们是
moving to something a bit different so
移动到一些不同的地方
Melanie promised to be to stay in time
梅兰妮承诺要及时
in the unit times in a reasonable time
在合理时间内在单位时间内
threat and when why while she is setting
威胁，以及为什么在她设定时
up okay okay so you you need to go to
起来好吧好吧，所以你需要去
this website
这个网站
that's it okay two things two things so
没关系，两件事，两件事，所以
one thing is that this is the t-shirts
一件事就是这是T恤
for the speaker of this year so I think
对于今年的演讲者，我想
that I'm happy with what we we design we
我对我们的设计感到满意
have this nice hashtag Community Builder
拥有这个漂亮的标签Community Builder
on the back so please pick up if you
在后面，所以如果你要接的话
speak at the conference don't forget to
在会议上讲话别忘了
pick up your your t-shirt and we will
拿起你的T恤，我们会
offer the the remaining tissue the
提供剩余的组织
leftover t-shirts just tomorrow at the
剩下的T恤就在明天
at the closing session so don't forget
在闭幕式上，别忘了
to pick up your your t-shirt before the
拿起你的T恤之前
closing session and so now she wants to
闭幕式，所以现在她想
start something new that you should go
开始一些你应该去的新事物
to mentees come on your smartphone
智能手机上的学员
that's another live interactive stuff
那是另一个现场互动的东西
and enter the code 24 41 43 let's go
然后输入代码24 41 43让我们开始
okay so you can as you want you can
好的，所以您可以随心所欲
connect at any at any moment so hi I'm
随时都可以连接，所以嗨，我是
melody buzz from hobby oh and so has
来自爱好的旋律嗡嗡声哦，还有
Gayle just said this is not exactly the
盖尔只是说这不完全是
same kind of thing I told them so one
我跟他们说过一样的话
did before but this would be a live
以前做过，但这将是现场直播
survey so I would not work you would
调查，所以我不会工作，你会
work the right now so I would need you
现在就工作，所以我需要你
to connect to Manta calm and then enter
连接到蝠ta镇静，然后进入
the code twenty four forty one forty
代码二十四十四四十一
sweet and so the purpose of this survey
甜，所以本次调查的目的
is to get your feedback about what
是为了获得您对什么的反馈
should be the future of folding tools
应该是折叠工具的未来
and this is I need your point of view so
这是我需要你的观点，所以
please answer to the survey
请回答调查
okay so at OBO we've been working on
好的，所以在OBO，我们一直在努力
modeling tools for quite a long time now
建模工具已有相当长的时间了
and we are used to work on the
我们习惯于
development of graphical tools and one
图形工具的开发和一
of our great success is serious so first
首先，我们取得巨大成功是非常认真的
one that does not know that does not
一个不知道那不
know anything about serious serious is a
知道什么有关严重严重是
framework to his alia and quickly create
他的别名的框架并快速创建
a graphical modeling workbench dedicated
专门的图形建模工作台
to your specific domain so when I talk
到您的特定域，所以当我讲话时
about graphical tools you know this is
关于图形工具，您知道这是
to tools with some squares and some
使用一些正方形和一些工具
pages and you try to make some relation
页面，您尝试建立一些关系
between these different forms so we are
这些不同形式之间，所以我们是
working on moving serious to the web and
致力于将严肃的东西转移到网络上
so we are looking for feedback about
所以我们正在寻找有关
hope modelling tools should evolve in
希望建模工具能够发展
the future according to your needs
根据您的需求的未来
the first question okay you all ready to
第一个问题好吗，你们都准备好了
answer the question you think that
回答您认为的问题
modeling tools should evolve in the
建模工具应在
future to be integrated in web
未来将集成到网络中
application desktop application here
应用程序桌面应用程序在这里
mobile devices and hey Clips ID so for
移动设备和嘿剪辑ID，因此
the moment you can still hunt sir okay
你仍然可以打猎的时候先生
continue we are around how many are we
继续，我们周围有多少人
50 60 okay go go go go go increase
50 60好的，走，走，走，走，走，增加
60 or more okay right wait
60或更多可以吧
are you sure that you can revert only
您确定只能还原
ones okay so 86 okay we're waiting for
可以，所以86可以，我们正在等待
the last 139 okay hi Taniya 1991 okay
最后的139好的，Taniya 1991好的
never stop so the first person sees that
永不停止，所以第一个人看到
you need web application then hey Clips
您需要Web应用程序，然后剪辑
ID and coming just after chair hands
ID和椅子手之后
here okay
好的
93 that's all okay next question what do
93没关系，下一个问题是什么
you expect from modeling in the future
您期望将来进行建模
free UK this is an open question so
自由英国这是一个悬而未决的问题，所以
please share what you are looking for
请分享您的寻找
modeling
造型
I'm sting talking about modeling in the
我很讨厌在谈论建模
future or nothing else
未来还是别的
so please
所以，请
there is some moderation but I don't
有一些节制，但我没有
know exactly if it works
确切知道它是否有效
oh please modeling NBIC easiness
哦，请为NBIC简便性建模
okay that's moving too fast for me
好吧，这对我来说太快了
simple modeling simple modeling with one
简单建模一个简单的建模
homer linguist to hell okay I'm waiting
荷马语言学家下地狱好吧我在等
for more answer domain make a better
为更多的答案域做一个更好的
world I would like to
我想要的世界
mmm execution routine - oh now ok money
mmm执行例程-哦，现在可以了
I would like that to incur money thanks
我想赚钱谢谢
to morning Hut sir
到早上先生
okay
好的
93 so that's one place Oh 98 100
93所以只有一个地方哦98 100
oh that's moles run more and more after
哦，那痣以后越来越多了
each question 100
每个问题100
okay thanks
好的谢谢
hmm okay maybe so next question
嗯好吧，所以下一个问题
so next one is what kind of features do
那么下一个是什么样的功能
you expect from the modeling tools
您对建模工具的期望
read-only diagrams editable diagrams
只读图可编辑图
tables trees charts dashboard chatbot
表树图表仪表板聊天机器人
photo layout 3d so on this question can
照片布局3d这样就可以
give points to the following pictures
给下面的图片点
and more you get more points you give
越多，您得到的积分就越多
the most important feature for you it
对您来说最重要的功能
will be represents
将代表
Heidi table diagrams okay
海蒂表图还可以
you
您
okay so chat bots are I'm pretty sure
好吧，我很确定聊天机器人
that you okay that's weird I think that
你好，那很奇怪，我认为
treaty was most important for us and
条约对我们和
chat bot but okay
聊天机器人，但是还可以
you
您
okay
好的
it's still moving can you vote multiple
它仍在移动，您能否投票多个
times this one also wrong no I don't
时代这一次也错了不，我不
think
认为
yes you need to scroll 85 okay
是的，您需要滚动85好的
86 87 is still moving okay
86 87仍然可以移动
I'm just waiting for the last one 91 92
我只是在等待最后一个91 92
that's all has really change from
这一切都从
bitches and chat but okay so but it's
ches子和聊天，但是还可以，但是
the last ones that's okay okay so next
最后一个还可以，所以接下来
question which is the last one and this
问题是最后一个，这个
is a quiz so the fastest to answer to
是测验，所以最快的答案
this question with one small gifts so
这个问题有一个小礼物，所以
are you ready
你准备好了吗
we're waiting for the last one again
我们在等最后一个
is that okay everyone is here start the
好的，每个人都在这里开始
question so what do you need to do
问题，所以你需要做什么
tomorrow morning
明天早上
take a chocolate in for your breakfasts
早餐吃巧克力
attend my 9:00 a.m. torque modeling goes
参加我上午9:00的扭矩建模
up to the cloud wake up with an ad hoc
临时到云中醒来
tapas party there is only one good
小吃派对只有一种
answer yeah so okay who is the winner so
回答是的，好的，谁是赢家，所以
the winner is
赢家是
so yes you should attend my talk
是的，你应该参加我的演讲
so the winner is I think that it's
所以胜利者是我认为
similar with Seema
与Seema类似
why are you okay so simmer you get you
你为什么还好，所以你就明白了
you have the privilege to get some
你有特权得到一些
glasses sunglasses yes that's your gift
眼镜太阳镜是你的礼物
you can there is more Sun for the one
你可以有更多的太阳
who wants there is some glasses some
谁想要一些眼镜
sunglasses also at the OBO booth so do
OBO展位上也有太阳镜
not hesitate you can have yours
毫不犹豫，你可以拥有你的
okay just to finish thanks to the
好的，要感谢
application you can ask me what you want
应用程序，你可以问我你想要什么
about the future of modeling tools and
关于建模工具的未来
loudly about the future of modern into
大声谈论现代的未来
brutes please so do not hesitate to add
蛮横的所以请不要犹豫添加
your questions and have no time right
您的问题，没有时间
now to answer them but tomorrow morning
现在要回答他们，但是明天早上
I could answer to those questions so do
我可以回答这些问题
not hesitate to type your different
毫不犹豫地键入您的不同
questions right now on this application
现在对此应用程序有疑问
and then include you so yeah expects I
然后包括你，所以我希望我
would be in the future hopefully so
希望将来如此
please enter a question and I will
请输入一个问题，我会
answer them tomorrow during my talk
明天在我的谈话中回答他们
thanks for a participation and see you
感谢您的参与，见到您
tomorrow morning
明天早上
thanks Melanie actually this platform is
谢谢梅兰妮，实际上这个平台是
entertain
招待
fun entertaining okay so thank you
好玩有趣，谢谢
everybody
大家
we will meet you what time do we start
我们会在什么时候见到您
7:30 so we meet you at 7:30 at the tone
7:30，我们将在7:30与您见面
at La Tomatina so well you have just
在La Tomatina很好，你只是
well just a bit of time to 7:30 tonight
今晚只有一点时间到7:30
at Latin Tina for the reception see you
在拉丁蒂娜接待处见
there and thanks bye
在那里，再见